(
"ai_sub_version": "3.5.2",
"generated_at": "2026-08-14T22:15:26.345581",
"lyrics_prompt_version": 9,
"subtitles_prompt_version": 18,
"complete": true,
"max_retries_exceeded": false,
"any_pending": false,
"settings": (
"ai": (
"model": null,
"model_subtitles": "google-gla:gemini-3.6-flash",
"model_lyrics": "google-gla:gemini-3.5-flash-lite",
"rpm": 4,
"tpm": 250000,
"google": (
"file_cache_ttl": 10,
"use_files_api": true,
"max_storage_gb": 18.0
),
"search": (
"qps": 0.3,
"max_length": 4096,
"web_search_tool": "langsearch",
"timeout": 60.0,
"retries": 3,
"min_wait_seconds": 1.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 10.0,
"multiplier": 2.0
),
"validation_buffer_ms": 2000,
"verification_gap_seconds": 60,
"gap_verification_retries": 1,
"gap_verification_ignore_start": true,
"gap_verification_ignore_end": true
),
"split": (
"max_seconds": 300,
"re_encode": (
"enabled": false,
"fps": 1.0,
"height": 360,
"bitrate_kb": 35,
"threshold_mb": 20,
"duration_tolerance_ms": 100,
"encoder": null
),
"start_offset_min": 0
"thread": (
"uploads": 4,
"re_encode": 2,
"lyrics": 4,
"subtitles": 4
),
"retry": (
"per_run": 5,
"max_runs": 3,
"multiplier": 2.0,
"min_wait_seconds": 30.0,
"max_wait_seconds": 300
),
"log": (
"level": "info",
"timestamps": true,
"scrub": false,
"progress_bars": true,
"progress_bar_width": 80,
"progress_bar_refresh_seconds": 1.0
)
ホロライブファンクラブ！
hololive Official Fan Club!
一条莉々華だよ！
It's Ichijou Ririka!
I'm Mori Calliope!
ホロライブファンクラブ 始まりました！
The hololive Official Fan Club has launched!
ここだけのオリジナルグッズや チケット先行抽選！
Exclusive original merchandise and advance ticket lotteries!
ほかにも楽しいコンテンツがいーっぱい！
Plus heaps of other fun content!
Campaigns too? That sounds really fun! I'm curious!
さあ、みんな！ ホロライブファンクラブで一緒に楽しもう！
Come on, everyone! Let's enjoy it together at the hololive Fan Club!
Join us now!
ここは露天風呂が有名だって言うから ずっと気になってたんだよね〜！
I heard the open-air bath here is famous, so I've been curious about it for a while~!
……ね、キミも一緒に行かない？ えっ！？ 一緒に入るって意味じゃないよ！？
...Hey, why don't you come with me? Eh!? I didn't mean taking a bath together!?
おーそーじ！ モココ、大掃除やってみたいんだよね！
Big cleaning! Mococo wants to try doing the year-end big cleanup!
もちろんキミも一緒にやるんだよ！？ じゃあ早速大掃除、開始だ〜！
Of course you're going to do it with me, right!? Alright then, let's start the big cleanup right now~!
え〜？ 服のすきまがどうしたって〜？
Eh~? What about the gap in my clothes~?
僕が掃除している間に、キミはいったいどこを見てたのかな〜？
While I was cleaning, where on earth were you looking, I wonder~?
お〜！ ここが夢にまで見た日本の温泉町〜♪
Wow~! This is the Japanese hot spring town I've dreamt of~♪
ん？ もしかして…… 私と一緒に入りたいなとか、思ってる？
Hm? Could it be... you're thinking you want to go in together with me?
……いいよ、一緒に入ろっか……？
...Okay, shall we go in together...?
……って、やばいやばい！ みんなそろそろカウントダウン始まるよ！
...Wait, oh no, oh no! Everyone, the countdown is about to start!
5、4、3、2、1……
5, 4, 3, 2, 1...
0！ ハッピーニューイヤー！
0! Happy New Year!
あけましておめでとうございます！ 今年もよろしくお願いします！
Happy New Year! I look forward to working with you again this year!
えへへ…… なんかあらためてかしこまると、はずかしくて照れちゃうね♪
Ehehe... Being formal like this again is a bit embarrassing and makes me blush♪
ダイヤモンド富士っていうんだっけ？ ほらほら！ だんだん富士山の輪郭が見えて来たよ！
Is it called Diamond Fuji? Look, look! The outline of Mount Fuji is gradually coming into view!
なんだかもう、この景色だけで感動するよ〜！
Gosh, I'm already moved just by this scenery~!
突然ですが、おせちを作りまーす！ つまみぐいしちゃダメだよ？
Suddenly, I'm going to make osechi! No sneaking a bite, okay?
もしつまみぐいしちゃったら…… ガブってちゃうからねっ！？
If you sneak a bite... I'm gonna bite you, you know!?
おめでとー！ おめでとー！ キミとぎゅーしながらお祝い♪
Happy New Year! Happy New Year! Celebrating while hugging you tight♪
キミをぎゅーできるのはモココだけなんだから！
Mococo is the only one who gets to hug you, after all!
ほらほらキミもモココのことぎゅーってして！
Come on, come on, you give Mococo a tight hug too!
せーの！ 今年もよろしくお願いします！
One, two! We look forward to another great year with you!
ホロライブ3期生
hololive 3rd Generation
次に挑む舞台は
The next stage they challenge is...
大作戦？
A Great Operation?
hololive 3rd Generation Live #きゅるるん大作戦 ～最強アイドル、推すしかないでしょ～
hololive 3rd Generation Live #KyururunGreatOperation ~The Ultimate Idols, You Have To Support Them!~
「好き」と「かわいい」を詰め込んで あなたと作る大作戦！
Packed with "love" and "cuteness," a great operation created with you!
いっぱいのこれまでと、ときめくような一瞬を！
Filled with all our history and a heart-fluttering moment!
どこまででもいけちゃう気がする #きゅるるん Oh yeah yeah
I feel like we can go anywhere! #Kyururun Oh yeah yeah
ちなみに作戦の内容は...
By the way, the details of the operation are...
とにかくかわいい！かわいいに満たされろ！
Simply cute! Be filled with cuteness!
作戦進行中！ #きゅるるん大作戦
Operation in progress! #KyururunGreatOperation
This is FLOW GLOW in COUNTDOWN LIVE!
来年もよろしくー！
Please treat us well next year too!
Let's go!
搭載V8エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
A hominid with a 7th sense
6するこの世界と全人類
In 6, this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
Changing the game with these 5
轟く4輪 発射せよ
4 roaring wheels, launch!
皆さん3キュウ サランヘヨ
Everyone, thank you, saranghaeyo
操る2台のturntable
Operating two turntables
獲る1番ここground 0
Taking #1 right here at ground 0
リスク超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond risk
チャンスもセットだ当然
Opportunities come with it, naturally
登りあげる頂点
Climbing up to the peak
座布団積んでく笑点
Stacking cushions like Shoten
乗り込むFG ROADSTER
Boarding the FG ROADSTER
特殊部隊 集合 能力者
Special forces, gathering powered beings
この歴史に名を彫る彫刻家
Sculptors carving our names into history
ぶっちぎりでおきざり後続車
Leaving behind the following cars far in the dust
今高速でぶち抜いていく大気圏
Rushing through the atmosphere at high speed now
エンジンからジェットの炎揺れている怪気炎
Jet flames from the engine, blazing strong
眼下に広がる大地を越えていく回帰線
Crossing tropic lines above the earth below
バックミラーにbig blueが映っているIBM
Big blue reflected in the rear view mirror, IBM
打ち上げ台から飛んでく
Flying off from the launchpad
うちら世代この燃料
This generation of ours is the fuel
朽ち果てないです銀河で
Never decaying in the galaxy
寿司食べたい
I want to eat sushi
見えてるでかいビジョン
Seeing a big vision
燃えてるメンバー一同
All members burning with passion
ただいま現在進行形
Currently in progress right now
超えてく世界規模
Surpassing global scale
叶うはずだ won't stop
It's bound to come true, won't stop
心臓がモンスター
My heart is a monster
aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光る tesla roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instinct
青い炎
Blue flame
bff let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unbound, from 0 to space
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
轟く booster
Roaring booster
flow glow the space to be
今 chase me
Now chase me
ターボ付きスーパーカー
A supercar with a turbo
ハンドルさばきはシューマッハ
Handling the wheel like Schumacher
副操縦士はチューバッカ
The co-pilot is Chewbacca
次元が違う連中ばっか
A gang from a whole different dimension
コーナー攻めてるギリギリ
Attacking corners right on the edge
モーター全開地響き
Motor full throttle, ground shaking
空から導き
Guided from the sky
お肌がピチピチ
Youthful and supple skin
タイヤ焦がしてドーナツターン
Burning tires doing donut turns
弾け飛んでくドラム缶
Oil drums flying around
顧客満足度高くて
Customer satisfaction is sky high
ぶち上がってるお客さん
The audience is super hyped up
0から最高到達点
From 0 to the highest peak
ためてる太陽光発電
Storing up solar power
探索するこの小惑星
Exploring this asteroid
超覚醒突入ボーナスステージ
Super awakening, entering bonus stage
一直線伸びてる道路
A road extending in a straight line
vibration エンジンの鼓動
Vibration, pulse of the engine
速度増し上がっている高度
Speed increasing, altitude climbing
限界、重力、凌駕し上昇
Surpassing limits and gravity, rising up
開拓しまくっていくフロンティア
Exploring frontier after frontier
旅立つ roadster only one
Setting off, roadster only one
アクセル踏み込んでくドンピシャ
Stepping on the gas right on point
飛んでく日本遺産
Flying off, Japanese heritage
1億馬力の重低音
100 million horsepower heavy bass
火星のホテルが休憩所
A hotel on Mars is our rest stop
並んで走行UFO
UFOs driving alongside us
降り立つ宇宙ステーション
Landing on the space station
物語を継承 まるで
Inheriting the story, like
旧約聖書 この先
The Old Testament, from here on
何世紀も成長生き延びて
Growing and surviving for centuries
結果出す take off
Delivering results, take off
叶うはずだ won't stop
It's bound to come true, won't stop
心臓がモンスター
My heart is a monster
aliens turn it up
FG party hard
光る tesla roadster
Shining Tesla Roadster
heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instinct
青い炎
Blue flame
bff let's go out, so get in the car
0から宇宙まで囚われず
Unbound, from 0 to space
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
轟く booster
Roaring booster
FLOW GLOW the space to be
今 chase me
Now chase me
以上、私達 FLOW GLOW でした！
That was FLOW GLOW!
こっから先も楽しんでいこう！
Let's keep having fun from here on!
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm
Infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
Look into my eyes, I'll seek you out
Reveal the truth and lies that you just can't hide
Clawing at the walls, I feel these sick temptations
What do I have to sacrifice?
Bound by a chain, desiring to do it my way
This hurricane of a devastating force is coming
Out of my veins, feel my pulse, it's rising and igniting
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of
becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Justice, it's just like that, I
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Make 'em fall down, make your, make your last wish
Make 'em, make 'em fall down, then they crash
Renegade, I'll make 'em
Bound by a vow, can I tread the waters lightly
Never making a sound, incognito, light the pathway
Burning 'em out, in the fallout I'll stand in the ashes
Fire
Snuff it out
Walking the line, on the edge of
becoming what I never thought I'd be
Better this than a goner
Take 'em all out, renegade
Walking the line, fell so far into poison
and I'm seeing me anew
Got ya, locked and I'm loaded
Take 'em all out, renegade
Justice, it's just like that, I
Don't care at all, I'll fall deeper 'til I can't quit
Never gon' stop 'cause I don't have a limit
My moral compass is out of focus
Renegade, I'll make it a little wicked
The light goes out
Tame the fire and fall before my justice
Final warning, you know my rage is limitless
On the advent of a new genesis, I'm
Infamous, yeah, I get a little villainous
The light goes out
ソラヲボエで挑む人生ゲーム
Taking on the game of life by rote memory,
言い訳めいたハートに従って
following a heart full of excuses.
現実半即興なプロットです
Reality is a semi-improvised plot,
取り憑かれるオーバーな芝居
an over-the-top performance that possesses us.
世渡り上手なあの子はね
That girl who's so good at playing the game,
二度と被った猫外せない
can never take off her innocent act.
痛みを知ってしまった magician
A magician who has come to know pain,
手の内はまだ明かせない
she still can't reveal her tricks.
yellow yellow ゼロからループ
Yellow, yellow, looping from zero,
点滅するピリオド
a blinking period.
yellow yellow 染まる紅い化粧
Yellow, yellow, painted in crimson makeup.
A world of 5,
can make or not
たとえ 好きに
Even if we're torn apart
離されても
at will,
No worries
私には 私がついて
I've got myself,
酔いが醒めるまで
Just a little longer
あと少しだけ
until I sober up,
真実を捉える残像
an afterimage capturing the truth—
Slow and steady win the race
slow and steady wins the race.
次の季節を越え
Beyond the next season,
Blooming Blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
please don't stop this sound.
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, ずっとStay gold
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, stay gold forever.
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
Looking to the mirror
Looking into the mirror,
絡まっている蜘蛛の糸
a tangled spider's thread,
It happens all the time
踊らされたって構わない
I don't care if I'm played.
陽気に憑いて
Possessed by cheerfulness,
時を編んで明けてくれて
weaving time and ushering in the dawn,
Always be honest
永遠に変わらないもの
something that never changes.
Yellow, yellow, 手を取り合えば
Yellow, yellow, if we join hands,
そこに理由は要らない
we don't need a reason.
Yellow, yellow, 染まる赤い結晶
Yellow, yellow, a dyed red crystal.
Atmosphere...
いくつになっても 希望に目移りして
No matter how old I get, distracted by hope,
途切れそうな運命や 人生ごと受け入れ
accepting every fragile fate and life as a whole.
1 2 3 4 Get down
君にウィング ポーズを決めて向かってGo Go
Striking a pose with wings for you, head forward, Go Go!
抱き続ける 3 1 7
Holding onto 3-1-7,
終着地点は Hell or Heaven
the final destination is Hell or Heaven.
No time to waste
今だけを信じて
believe only in the present,
最後のフィナーレまで ともに進め
press forward together until the final finale!
酔いが醒めるまで
Just a little longer
あと少しだけ
until I sober up,
真実を捉える残像
an afterimage capturing the truth—
Slow and steady win the race
slow and steady wins the race.
次の季節を越え
Beyond the next season,
Blooming Blooming
どうかこの音を止めないで
please don't stop this sound.
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, ずっとStay gold
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow, stay gold forever.
Our time yellow, yellow, let it flow, let it flow
Let's enjoy the moment
またね！
See you!
またね〜
See ya~
楽しかったー！
That was so much fun!
ReGLOSSでした！バイバーイ！
We were ReGLOSS! Bye-bye!
Time to open up your eyes,
feel the music start to rise,
got to break the world and let me in.
I know I was meant to be
livin' life so fast and free,
try to keep your eyes on me,
'cause this is where my story all begins!
Livin' it up like crazy
ready to play? Come at me
carried away so easy,
I can't get enough!
Free as a bird, no limit
haven't you heard? I'm fearless
get up and go, let's do this!
Watch me, watch me, watch me...
Watch me be your diva,
I'm gonna raise your fever,
shakin' up all the crowd,
making some noise when I'm not allowed,
livin' my life out loud,
I have awakened to wisdom beyond understanding,
(I keep indulging in my every whim)
Let it out!
(Oh, o-oh, o-oh)
Don't blame me if I shine too bright
Can't help it if I start a fight
(Oh, o-oh, o-oh)
Now pay attention, please
'cause this is only the beginning -
It's our genesis!
Coming to wreak some havoc,
how do you like this plot twist?
I'm embracing my madness.
(Can you hear it?)
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings,
I'm destined for great things!
I'm sure you've heard of me by now.
Woah~
Midnight, draw me to the dark side,
Daylight, take me on a joyride,
My crime is my passion,
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is:
This is our genesis.
Ooh~ Gonna start the rave,
when I misbehave, take center stage
Ooh~ Let the fun commence,
but you know I'm gonna get intense
There are loopholes unspoken;
the rules can all be broken,
I'm runnin' on a rampage,
the world is a blank page
I'm writing my story in flames and in glory,
They're gonna know me by name!
(Oh, o-oh o-oh)
Is this my promised land?
The future's in my hands.
(Oh, o-oh o-oh)
But they don't understand
That I'm a star in the making,
Bow-bow-bow-bow
Tell me how you like me now?
Yeah! Yeah!
Let's celebrate the New Year!
Watch me, watch me, watch me, watch me
Let your worries go, gonna show you how to lose control, ready?
You've got to free your mind
Leave your restraint behind
Be outrageous, the chaos is contagious
Come on, you know what time it is!
It's our genesis!
Time to open up your eyes
Feel the music start to rise
Got to break the world and let me in
I know I was meant to be
Livin' life so fast and free
Try to keep your eyes on me
'Cause this is our beginning
It's our genesis!
Whispers banging down your window
Rumors reaching a crescendo
No humble beginnings, I'm destined for great things
I'm sure you've heard of me by now, whoa-oh
Midnight, draw me to the dark side
Daylight, take me on a joyride
My crime is my passion
I'm mayhem in action
I know what day it is
This is our genesis!
You know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is?
Yeah, you know what time it is?
It's our genesis!
Tell me what time it is?
2nd STAGE
君に届けたい
I want to reach you
id:entity
素敵な君に一歩を踏み出した
I took a step forward to the wonderful you
おはよう！こんばんは！
Good morning! Good evening!
この世界に叫んでみよう
Let's shout out to this world!
本日のライブではどれの自分を見せるの？
Which self will I show at today's concert?
前から悩んで好きな自分になれない
I've been worrying for a long time, unable to become the self I love
そしてある日誰かに言われた
And then one day, someone said to me...
痛い言葉に迷っていた
I was lost amidst painful words
いつも作る笑顔失わないように
Trying not to lose the smile I always put on
これ以上は期待を裏切らないと決めた
I decided not to betray expectations anymore
溢れている雑音の中
Amidst the overflowing noise
この声響けるか？
Can this voice resound?
心に宿る声を聞いてみよう
Let's listen to the voice residing in our heart
これはずっと見せたかった自分だった
This was the self I always wanted to show
集まった声たちが一つになる id:entity
The gathered voices become one id:entity
月日がすぎてやっとスポットライトに
As time passed, finally under the spotlight
立てるけれど少しだけ怖くなった
I can stand here, but I became a little scared
でもね一人じゃない仲間たちがいるんだ
But you know, I'm not alone, my friends are here
家族みたいな絆で違いが分かり合えた
With a bond like family, we understood our differences
それぞれに輝きがあって
Each has their own shine
ハーモニー奏でるかな？
Will we play a harmony?
手をつないで一緒に夢のその先へ
Holding hands, let's go beyond that dream together
精一杯歓声をあげましょう
Let's cheer with all our might
幸せを届けるんだ
We will deliver happiness
どこにだって響かせよう
Let's make it resound everywhere
新しい舞台に飛び込んで今...
Diving into a new stage now...
チャンスを 躊躇わないで
Don't hesitate when given a chance
ここにずっと 秘めた音色が
The melody hidden here all this time
独自のハーモニーになって
Becomes our unique harmony
心の迷いが消えていく
And the doubts in our hearts fade away
これからずっと 自分のままで
From now on, staying true to ourselves
集まった声たちが
All these gathered voices
違っても 揺るがないと信じて
Even if different, believing they won't falter
ひとつになる ID:entity
Becoming one ID:entity
オハヨウ! コンバンワ! お疲れ様でした!
Good morning! Good evening! Thank you for your hard work!
オハヨウ! コンバンワ! また会う日まで
Good morning! Good evening! Until the day we meet again
我ら エデンの星を統べる者！
We are the rulers of Planet Eden!
秘密結社 holoX！
Secret Society holoX!
でござる！
De gozaru!
時は熟した！2026年を待つ貴様ら！
The time has come! You bastards awaiting 2026!
準備はいいかー！
Are you ready?!
Are you ready?
夜が深まる ほら Darkness
Night deepens, look, Darkness
ノワール 鷹の羽で隠す
Concealing Noir with hawk feathers
縄に従えと Instinct
Instinct tells you to obey the leash
頭に参上 サムライ屋
Samurai shop arriving at the master's presence!
闇討ちしないけど
We won't launch a surprise attack, but...
奪う心
...stealing your heart...
提出でオッケー
...is totally fine to hand over!
斬りたくなかった
I didn't want to cut you down!
悪の手のひら 踊りたくなる
On the palm of evil, you'll want to dance
ほら君も 気づけばノリノリで
Look, before you know it, you're getting into the groove!
どうしようもない どうしようもない 落ちてく運命
Helpless, completely helpless, a falling fate
逃げ場がない もう全部 塗り替えよう
There's nowhere to run, let's repaint it all!
エクスデス エクスデス エクスデスが 交差する真ん中で
At the center where Exodus, Exodus, Exodus intersects
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト 世界はもう 始まっている
Next, Next, Next, the world has already begun
Jump! 飛びな 飛びな 闇が寄る方へ
Jump, jump towards where darkness gathers!
暗黒のエクスデス
The Dark Exodus!
混沌としたこの世界を
This chaotic world...
我ら holoX 色に塗り替えるのだ！
...we shall repaint in holoX colors!
皆の者、従え！
Everyone, obey!
Yes, My Dark!
アブソリュート・ダークネス・インフィニティ！
Absolute Darkness Infinity!
来年こそ世界征服！
Next year, world domination for sure!
メガ・ホークアイ！
Mega Hawkeye!
はい、今見ているみなさんはもう holoX 員ですよ！
Yes, everyone watching right now is already a holoX member!
かなりイイ麻酔！
Pretty good anesthesia!
2026年もずーっと一緒だよ！
We'll be together all through 2026 too!
風の先まで かがり火焚き！
Lighting bonfires to the end of the wind!
一刀両断 斬り捨て御免！
Severing with a single stroke, pardon my blade!
どうしようもない どうしようもない 落ちてく運命
Helpless, completely helpless, a falling fate
逃げ場がない もう全部 塗り替えよう
There's nowhere to run, let's repaint it all!
刮目せよ！
Pay close attention!
エクスデス エクスデス エクスデスが 交差する真ん中で
At the center where Exodus, Exodus, Exodus intersects
ネクスト ネクスト ネクスト 世界はもう 始まっている
Next, Next, Next, the world has already begun
Jump! 飛びな 飛びな 闇が寄る方へ
Jump, jump towards where darkness gathers!
笑うのは
The ones who laugh...
holoX で！
...will be holoX!
我らが秘密結社 holoX！
Our Secret Society holoX!
Run back 'round...
Don't stop now...
Up with the moonlight
Down in the streetlights
Looking for a spotlight
Making my move
I'm running
Let's go!
Days like a whirlwind don't stop coming
Got me in a tailspin
What can I do?
Keep running!
Let's go!
Lost and found, back to where I started
I won't stay down, trust me, I can do it!
I live life loud, take it to the limit
So stand up proud, now I'm gonna sing it!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Sparks on the pavement
Dreams in the distance
Gotta be relentless
Faster than sound
Keep running!
Let's go!
Lock it and load it, we're explosive
Swifter and lighter, tomorrow's brighter
Faster than lightning, about to get exciting
Come on, get ready, it's a new dawn!
Run back 'round, it's a new beginning
I run back 'round, got to keep believing
I run back 'round, I know where I'm going
I run back 'round, nothing's gonna stop me now!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
走して 走して 走して
Keep running, keep running, keep running
I'm gonna run back 'round!
始まるよ
It's starting!
憧れの
The dream we longed for...
Look at this dream this way
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Everybody
どこまでも
To wherever
今から Come on!
Starting now, come on!
I'm gonna run back 'round!
Hololive! You guys ready?
To greet the new year? Hell yeah!
No time to waste!
Let's get it started!
単純なフレーズで catch して
Catching on with a simple phrase
困難だらけの人生だけど
It's a life full of hardships, but...
自由奔放に slap して 楽しんじゃおう
Let's slap freely and just enjoy it!
立ちはだかる壁なんて 3秒で knock out
Knock out any wall standing in the way in 3 seconds!
止まらないんじゃないの 止まれないんだ!
It's not that I won't stop—I can't stop!
Slap by step で 空中散歩 私なりで
Walking on air slap by step, in my own way
隙あればその瞬間 完全知識
If there's an opening, taking complete control in an instant
沼にハマっちゃうぞ!
You'll fall head over heels!
One, two, three で 深層心理 crash して
Crashing into deep psychology on one, two, three
ツマラナイ
Shoot through
現実を
this boring reality
常識外れの rifle で 撃ち抜いて!
with an unconventional rifle!
ぐるぐる宇宙侵入して!
Invading the spinning universe!
Ah 極彩色の dance floor
Ah, on the colorful dance floor!
とんだ無礼ね 平手打ちよ
How terribly rude! Here's a slap for you!
子供扱いしないで
Don't treat me like a child!
ニヤついた顔に slash it!
Slash it on that smirking face!
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
首飛んじゃっても為せば成る
Even if my head flies off, where there's a will...
それが theory さ
...there's a way, that's the theory!
Clap your hands and stand up, please!
つべこべ言わずに着いてきて
Follow us without talking back!
Ready? It's time for the show
We're ignited, and have no fear,
ready to break through.
姿
Our appearances...
形は
...and forms...
違っても同じ思いだ
...may be different, but our feelings are the same!
そうだから...!
That's why...!
Slap by step で空中散歩 私なりで
Slap by step, walking on air in my own way!
隙あらば
If there's an opening...
その瞬間に完全掌握
...we'll completely take over in an instant!
沼にハマっちゃうぞ!
You're gonna fall deep into the swamp!
One, two, three で深層心理 crash して
Crash into deep psychology on one, two, three!
今すぐね
Right now!
私たちの色に染め上げた
We'll show you a world...
世界を見せる!
...dyed entirely in our colors!
皆様、今年の応援もありがとうございましたわ！
Everyone, thank you so much for your support this year as well!
HoloIDはもっともっと盛り上がるよ！
HoloID is going to get even more exciting!
ずっと見ててね！
Keep watching us!
来年もよろしくお願いします！
Please support us next year too!
See you next year!
Ahem! 皆さん、森カリオペです！
Ahem! Everyone, I'm Mori Calliope!
What's up? Hololive English -Myth- coming right at you for a brand new year!
今年、すごい盛り上がったね！
It got super hype this year!
来年もよろしく！
Looking forward to next year too!
We're gonna rock the world 10 times harder next year. You in? Next up, Ina!
Wah! Hello everyone, this is Ina!
Thank you so much for a really fun 2025!
今年、すごく楽しかったです！
I had so much fun this year!
来年もよろしくお願いしますね！
Please treat us well next year too!
Yeah, let's go!
Next is Kiara!
キケリキー！小鳥遊キアラです！
Kikeriki~! It's Takanashi Kiara!
キアラらしく盛り上げるぞー！
Let me hype you up Kiara-style!
Dankeschön! Love! Come on!
We love you!
All right! Let's have fun in 2026, too!
Let's go! ガチでやりましょうか！
Let's go! Shall we really go all out?
2026年もよろしくー！
Please support us in 2026 too!
All right, let's show them what we got!
There's an answer out there somewhere
When the muses whisper "Truth or dare?"
The hands of fate play tug-of-war
But no one's keeping score
Stay the course and be tenacious
'Cause the future is a game of chance
The chips are down, but I'm all in
I play until I win
I'm not gonna give up now
The wheels of fortune circle back around
A new turn in the betting ring
A maze of outcomes drawn in golden string
And through this tangled thread,
I see what's up ahead:
A wild chase,
a frantic pace,
I got to try my luck, I'm spinning fate
I'm always spinning fate
Spin the roulette, see where it falls
Testing the limits and betting it all
Round and around, jumping into the circle
Over and over, a test of will
Oh, the game is never easy
And the outcome is a mystery
But these are fates worth betting on,
Their threads unbroken
Called to life by flaxen string,
Casting lots together at the start of everything
I'm not gonna give up yet,
I spin back 'round with every chance I get
...the die is cast
The time has come for fate to change at last
And if it's black or red, I'm moving up ahead!
A perfect chance, a daring dance
I'll spin this thread of fate with my own hands
I'm taking fate into my hands
And through this tangled thread, I see what's up ahead
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び出そう
Hyper Jumpin', let's jump out!
Come on baby 輝いて Heart キュンとパピラ
Come on baby, shine bright, heart throbbing with excitement!
Hyper Jumpin' 夢の先までもっと
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond our dreams, more and more,
もっと刺激が欲しいの
I want more excitement!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
子供じゃない はしゃぐ方がお得でしょう
Not a kid, but having fun is better, right?
テイクアップから劃い上がっていくテンション
Rising high from take-off, our tension climbs!
余韻のなか 打ち返しまくるモーション
Striking back repeatedly amidst the afterglow!
カーブを乗りこなして進むミッション
Navigating the curves, progressing through our mission!
このままスピード加速して
Accelerating our speed just like this,
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
what awaits us at our destination?
止まらない気持ちは助走つけて
Building momentum with unstoppable feelings,
次元を超えていこう
let's go beyond dimensions!
さあ Hyper Jumpin' 飛び跳ねよう ハイになってハイになるまで楽しげな
Now, Hyper Jumpin', let's leap up high, having fun until we get super high!
Hyper Jumpin' 空の向こうまでもっともっと近づきたいの
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sky, I want to get closer and closer!
ドキドキしたい Give me Give me Love
I want heart-throbbing thrills, give me give me love!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Hyper Jumpin'
斜めから攻めて解決クエスチョン
Attacking from an angle to solve the question!
ネガティブを切り裂いてくれるチェンソー
A chainsaw cutting through all the negativity!
流れるコメントと掛け合いセッション
A call-and-response session with scrolling comments!
エイムを鍛えて狙い打つフリクション
Training our aim to target precision friction!
好きなまま Bang Bang Bang! 邪魔するノイズは打ち消せ Bang Bang Bang!
Just as you like, Bang Bang Bang! Silence interfering noise, Bang Bang Bang!
感動したいだけ 味わう実質で 笑い飛ばして 蹴飛ばせ Kick In!
Just wanting to be moved, savoring the real deal, laugh it off, kick it away, Kick In!
このまま僕らは旅をして
Just like this, we continue our journey,
たどり着く先に何があるんだろう
what awaits us at our destination?
信じた未来とリンクして
Linking with the future we believed in,
次元を超えていこう
let's go beyond dimensions!
さあ
Now,
Hyper Jumpin' 飛び越えよう ハイになってハイになるまで楽しげな
Hyper Jumpin', let's leap over, having fun until we get super high!
Hyper Jumpin' 海の向こうまでもっともっと近づきたいの
Hyper Jumpin', even beyond the sea, I want to get closer and closer!
ドキドキしたい Give me Give me Love
I want heart-throbbing thrills, give me give me love!
もっともっと高く飛びたいの
I want to jump higher and higher!
Hyper Jumpin' Now!
Bukalah mata dan bangunkan diri
Open your eyes and awaken yourself,
Tiada waktu 'tuk bermimpi
there's no time to dream.
Dunia akan...
The world will...
我らの蘇り
Our resurrection...
鏡に映る 心に宿っている
Reflected in the mirror, dwelling in my heart...
小さな光
...is a tiny light.
そう 今も感じる どこか心の奥で
Yes, I can still feel it somewhere deep in my heart,
目を覚ました
It has awakened.
忘れられない 浮かぶメモリー
Unforgettable memories floating back,
今の自分になる その前に
Before I became who I am today.
派手のない 音色でも唯一
An unglamorous tone, yet unique on its own.
探していた 落ちてくる どこまでも
And twilight falls everywhere, without end.
引き締める 鎖がまた 体を止めてた
Tightening chains once again held my body back,
ためらいを覚えてしまって 凍えていくの
Having learned hesitation, I freeze up.
明日の向こう側には 未知なるエリア
Beyond tomorrow lies an unknown area,
その境界線の先で待つのは 15の始まり
Beyond that boundary, what awaits is the start of 15!
蠢き 訳分からず
Squirming around without understanding why,
奈落の底へと 落ちていく
Falling down to the bottom of the abyss.
進化も 観測もしない
Neither evolving nor being observed,
時計の針の音 立っていられず
Unable to stand the sound of the ticking clock.
記憶に残る 広がる海
Remaining in memory, the expanding ocean,
届いたの 知らない森の中に
Reached deep into an unknown forest.
宇宙を超え 逃げ場探して
Crossing the cosmos, searching for a refuge,
そんな格好のまま 頭に響いている
Remaining like that, echoing in my head.
解けない鎖を断ち 切れないままもがき
Unable to sever the unbreakable chains, struggling on,
物語の始まり 探し続けたい
I want to keep searching for the start of the story.
宇宙の奥深くに 謎のような言葉さ
Deep within space, words like a riddle,
この体の中で 目覚めた 本当の姿
Awakened inside this body: my true form!
運命の カードが 裏返るため
So that the cards of fate may turn over,
真相へ 向かい 終わらない
Heading towards the truth, never ending!
解き放つ 鎖が消え 進めると信じて
Unleashed, the chains vanish, believing I can move forward,
新たな自分になって 光の方へ
Becoming a new self towards the light!
描いた通り 築いた 未知なるエリア
Built just as envisioned, an unknown area,
その境界線を越える日が来た 15はこれから
The day has come to cross that boundary; 15 starts now!
信じあう 仲間と一緒に
Together with comrades who trust each other,
挑戦の 狼煙をあげよう
Let's raise the signal fire of challenge!
終わらない
An endless...
青春へ
...youth story!
ぶつかり合って 喧嘩をして平気じゃん
Clashing and fighting with each other is totally fine, right?
みんなで揃えば
As long as we're all together...
逃げる 追いついていけ 頑張れ 落ち込んで
Running, catch up, hang in there, feeling down...
青春 演じているの？ あっちゅーま
Are we playing the role of youth? In the blink of an eye!
成長した姿を見せたい
I want to show you how much I've grown.
ギバー？ 完璧！ 本番はもっと全力で
Giver? Perfect! During the real show, give it even more all-out effort!
ハイ！ ハイ！ ハイ！
Hi! Hi! Hi!
大切な思い出 たくさんあるけどね
I have so many precious memories, but...
まだ
Still,
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
there's no time to indulge in sentimentality!
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting!
想像の果てにある高み
A height at the end of imagination...
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな 限界の壁超えて
Don't run away! Overcome the wall of limits!
僕らは まだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
イェイ！
Yeah!
詰めていく声に溺れてった
Drowning in pressing voices,
微かな望みを引き寄せるように
as if trying to grasp a faint trace of hope.
期待外れだと誰かが嘆く
Someone laments that it's a disappointment.
痛いと痛いがいつも戦う
Pain clashes with pain all the time.
プライドだけを頼りに抗う
Resisting, relying only on pride,
自分を信じたい
I want to believe in myself.
努力は報われる？
Will effort be rewarded?
笑いたい奴は笑ってろ
Let whoever wants to laugh, laugh!
感傷に浸ってる暇はない
There's no time to indulge in sentimentality.
今世紀最大の夏が始まる
The greatest summer of this century is starting!
反響が足りない もっともっと
The echo isn't enough, more and more!
後悔はさせない
I won't let you regret it!
想像の果てにある高み
A height at the end of imagination...
勝ち取った景色は尊い
The scenery we won is precious.
逃げるな 限界の壁超えて
Don't run away! Overcome the wall of limits!
僕らは まだチャレンジャー
We are still challengers!
イェイ！
Yeah!
4th STAGE
[Title: 4th STAGE]
夢見る空へ
[Song Title: To the Sky of Dreams]
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding joined hands tightly without letting go...
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
Here we go, let's head towards the dreaming sky!
窓越しに見上げた
Looking up through the window,
とても小さな空
at a very small sky.
ここで出会えたのは
What we met here were
数え切れない奇跡
countless miracles.
繰り返し踏み出す一歩が
Every step taken again and again
きらめきをつないで
connects the sparkle,
星のような笑顔
smiles like stars...
導いてくれた
guided us here.
Day by Day
みんなの声が力になる
everyone's voice becomes our strength.
Stage by Stage
ここでそれぞれ目指すもの
what each of us aims for here,
それぞれ描くもの
what each of us paints,
それぞれ願った夢
the dreams each of us wished for!
重ねた手はぎゅっと離さずに
Holding joined hands tightly without letting go...
一人一人違う色で描く
Each of us painting with a different color...
ときめき
heart-fluttering excitement.
振り向くことなくまっすぐに
Straight forward without turning back,
行くよ 行こう 夢見る空へ
here we go, let's head towards the dreaming sky!
笑い合ったことや
The things we laughed about,
尽きそうにない話題
topics that never seemed to run out...
思い出でいっぱいなのに
Even though we're filled with memories...
あの日生むの日々
Those days that gave birth to that day,
上書きじゃなくて 名前つけて保存
without overwriting, saving with a name.
どれも全部大事で
Every single one is precious,
生きていける
enabling us to live on.
みんなの顔が力になる
Everyone's faces give us strength.
今日も賑やかすぎるくらい
Today is so lively,
笑顔がもう止まらない
our smiles just won't stop.
想いは膨らんでいく
Our feelings keep growing bigger.
重ねた今 ぎゅっと噛みしめて
Treasure this present moment we've built together,
ひとりひとり違う声で 歌うから広がる
as our different voices sing and spread far and wide.
風を感じたら まっすぐに 行くよ
When we feel the wind, we'll head straight forward...
行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, toward the sky of our dreams!
憧れ 手を伸ばし
Reaching out our hands to our aspirations,
掴み取った その光が
the light that we grasped...
いつの日か
Someday,
また誰かの憧れに変わる
will turn into someone else's dream to chase.
繋げよう
Let's pass it on!
重ねた手は ぎゅっと離さずに
Holding our joined hands tightly without letting go,
ひとりひとり違う色で 描きだすときめき
each of our distinct colors paints this excitement.
出会えたすべてに ありがとう
Thank you to everyone we've met.
奇跡だって起こし続け ずっとそばにいるよ 行くよ
We'll keep making miracles happen and stay by your side...
行こう 夢見る空へ
Let's go, toward the sky of our dreams!
Hololive GAMERS!
We are GAMERS !!!!
せーの！ We are GAMERS !!!!
Ready, set, go! We are GAMERS !!!!
ミオーん！
Mio-n!
こーん！とキツネが登場 白髪ケモミミ白上フブキです
Kon! A fox appears! White-haired beast-eared Shirakami Fubuki here!
突っ込んでちゃ始まらない 君もすこん部に入部しなさい
Standing around won't get you anywhere, join the Sukonbu club!
ハイ！ イェーイ！ ハイ！ イェーイ！
High! Yeah! High! Yeah!
古今東西コーン茶をチョーダイ
Give me corn tea anytime, anywhere!
AIじゃないし得意はMC 赤い恋より金の鯉が推し
I'm not an AI and my specialty is MCing; I prefer golden carp over red love!
ミオしゃ〜！
Miosha~!
うちうちうちだよ大神ミオだよ 黒髪ケモミミ狼 (みおーん！)
It's me, me, me, Ookami Mio! Black-haired beast-eared wolf! (Mio-n!)
ツッ込んで止めます like a ママ 笑い出すと止まらない ゲラゲラ
I jump in to handle things like a mama, and once I start laughing, I can't stop!
つまり実はポンってコト？！
So basically, I'm a bit clumsy?!
小足ステップしちゃう音
Stepping lightly with tiptoe sounds!
タロット占いを見る未来 ホラーゲームはやられたくなぁい！
Seeing the future with Tarot fortune-telling, but I don't wanna play horror games!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強 君も遊ぼうよ Bダッシュ
When the 4 of us gather, Gamers are the strongest! Play with us, B-dash!
クリア目指してレベル上げ 今日は何プレイしよう
Leveling up to aim for clear, what shall we play today?
君のハートも攻略しちゃう 選択をしてシミュレーション
Conquering your heart too, making choices in a simulation!
初見も古参に対よろ やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
First-timers or long-time fans, nice meeting you! Games are so fun after all!
We are GAMERS !!!!
おかゆ〜！
Okayu~!
いっくよー もぐもぐ 猫又おかゆ
Here I go, mogumogu, Nekomata Okayu!
おにぎり おにぎり はいどうぞー
Rice balls, rice balls, here you go!
きらきら ふらふら しょーない猫だもん
Sparkling, wandering, I'm just a helpless cat.
ふーん そっかぁ 僕でよくない？
Hmm, is that so? Wouldn't I be good enough?
まったりゆっくり跳ねるリズム 全肯定するおかゆイズム
Laid-back, slow, bouncing rhythm, all-affirming Okayu-ism!
全行程 効率OK
All processes, efficiency OK!
毎日僕といっしょー！
Together with me every day!
ころね〜！
Korone~!
おぁよ〜 ゆびゆび ワンワン
Morning~ Yubi-yubi! Woof-woof!
パンをコネコネ 戌神ころね
Kneading bread dough, Inugami Korone!
犬種：キャバリア・キング・チャールズ・スパニエル
Breed: Cavalier King Charles Spaniel!
懐くけど圧かける 訛るイントネーション
Friendly but pressuring, accented intonation!
割れるリアクション
Loud reactions!
まずは指を捧げてくれる？ 配信ショー
First, can you offer up your fingers? Stream show!
わかったー なほーね 指示厨オッケー
Got it, I see! Backseat gamers OK!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
When all four of us are together, Gamers are the strongest!
フラグが立てばすぐ回収
If a flag is raised, we instantly resolve it!
エイム鍛えて狙い撃ち
Sharpening our aim for the sniped hit!
今日は何プレイしよう
What shall we play today?
君のハートを回復しちゃう
We'll restore your heart!
ワクワクするねこのダンジョン
This dungeon is so exciting, isn't it?
「耐久」っていうか止められない
It's not just an "endurance stream", we can't stop!
だってゲームが好きなんだもん
Because we just love games so much!
「突然ですが、ボーナスチャレンジの時間です。」
"Out of nowhere, it's time for a bonus challenge!"
「大きな声でレスポンスをして高得点を狙いましょう！」
"Shout your responses loud and aim for a high score!"
Are you ready?
せーの！ こーんこんっ！
Say! Kon kon!
こーんこんっ！
Kon kon!
せーの！ みょーんみょーん！
Say! Myon myon!
みょーんみょーん！
Myon myon!
せーの！ もぐもぐ！
Say! Mogu mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
せーの！ ゆびゆび！
Say! Yubi yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
せーの！ こーんこんっ！
Say! Kon kon!
こーんこんっ！
Kon kon!
せーの！ みょーんみょーん！
Say! Myon myon!
みょーんみょーん！
Myon myon!
せーの！ もぐもぐ！
Say! Mogu mogu!
もぐもぐ！
Mogu mogu!
せーの！ ゆびゆび！
Say! Yubi yubi!
ゆびゆび！
Yubi yubi!
お〜〜っ！！
Woooh!!
4人揃えばゲーマーズ最強
When all four of us are together, Gamers are the strongest!
上手く行かなくてもコンティニュー
Even if things don't go well, we continue!
全クリするまで諦めない
We won't give up until we 100% clear it!
エンディングを見に行こう
Let's go see the ending!
君のハートも攻略しちゃう
We'll win over your heart too!
選択をしてシミュレーション
Making choices and simulating!
初見も古参も対よろ
First-timers and long-time fans, GLHF!
やっぱりゲームは楽しいね
Games really are the best after all!
We are GAMERS!!!!
こうして2025年の幕が閉じるのであった――
And so, the curtain fell on the year 2025...
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this brand-new excitement resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best times, with the best friends!
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle!
覚えてるかな 最初の歌
Do you remember our very first song?
懐かしいね
It brings back memories...
私 声が震えていた
My voice was shaking back then.
すごく緊張...
I was so nervous...
あの日から続く未来は
The future that continued from that day...
みんなと掴んだ今日だよ
...is this today we seized together with everyone!
もっともっともっともっと 加速するハート
Faster and faster, our accelerating hearts!
一緒に行こうどこまでも
Let's go together, wherever it takes us!
Are you ready? 準備は OK?
Are you ready? Are you good to go?
ひらけ 夢の扉を
Open up the door of dreams!
1 2 3 キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
生まれたてのドキドキを響かせよう
Let's make this brand-new excitement resound!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
The best times, with the best friends!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm right here, because you found me!
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ
I came here because I wanted to meet you!
みんなで歌おう 終わらないメロディー
Let's all sing a never-ending melody together!
キラメキに乗って
Riding on the sparkle!
届いてるかな 私の声
Can you hear my voice reaching you?
ハッキリと
Loud and clear...
届けたいのは君に笑顔
What I want to deliver to you is a smile!
スマイル
A smile!
理想の遠さに悔しんで
Frustrated at how far away our ideals felt,
みんなと泣き笑ったね
we cried and laughed together with everyone!
ギュッとギュッとギュッとギュッと すべて抱きしめて
Tightly, tightly holding onto everything!
一緒に行こうどこまでも
Let's go together, wherever it takes us!
Are you ready? 準備は OK?
Are you ready? Are you good to go?
進め 自分の道を
Forge ahead on your own path!
1 2 3 キラメキライダー
1, 2, 3, Kirameki Rider!
好きな気持ち カラフルに奏でたいな
I want to play my loving feelings in full color!
最高の場所 最高のみんなと
The best stage, with the best people!
ここにいるよ 幻なんか...
I'm right here—this isn't an illusion...
まだ 終わらない
Still not over,
君の心が 幸せに染まるように
May your heart be filled with happiness
重ねていく ハーモニー
As we layer our harmony,
きらめき纏って
Adorned in sparkling light.
歌い続けたいな
I want to keep singing,
踊り続けたいな
I want to keep dancing.
そんな願いは ワガママじゃないでしょ？
That wish isn't selfish, is it?
だって 楽しすぎて
Because it's so much fun,
もう 止まらない
I can't stop anymore!
輝くステージで
On this shining stage,
もっと もっと
More and more,
ずっと...
Forever...
嬉しい 楽しい 愛しい だけじゃ 語れない
Happy, fun, and dear alone can't describe it.
今も 今も 悩みはあるけど
Even now, even now, there are worries, but...
ここにいるよ 私 ここにいるよ
I am right here, I am right here!
君と同じ世界を 見つめて
Gazing upon the same world as you...
行くよ！ きらめきの中で
Here we go! In the middle of this sparkle,
生まれたての ドキドキを 響かせよう
Let's sound this freshly born excitement!
最高の時間 最高の仲間と
This best of times, with the best of friends!
ここにいるよ 見つけてくれたから
I'm here because you found me!
君に会いたくてやってきたんだ みんなで歌おう
I came here wanting to see you! Let's all sing together!
終わらないメロディ
An never-ending melody,
きらめきに乗って
Riding on the sparkle,
きらめき纏って
Adorned in sparkling light!
Yeah!
2025年もあと少し！
2025 is almost over!
みんな盛り上がってるー？
Is everyone hyped up?
今回はカウントダウンライブ！
This time it's a Countdown Live!
あれ？ あれれ？
Huh? Wait a second...
コメントの流れる速度、なんか少なくない？
Aren't the comments flowing a bit slow?
まだまだ足りない！ こんなのー！
It's still not enough! Not like this!
この この この この...
Kono, kono, kono, kono...
浮気は 許しません
Cheating on me is not allowed!
私だけに 注目してね
Pay attention only to me, okay?
私だけに 一途？ っち！
Faithful only to me? Tch!
単推しじゃなきゃ やだやだ！
If you're not a single-stan, I hate it, hate it!
絶叫！
Scream!
ぷんぷん！ 激おこ！ ぷんぷん！ ちょ、ちょ、ちょっと待って！
Pout! Furious! Pout! Wa-wa-wait a minute!
よそ見したら
If you look away,
ブー！ ブー！ ブー！ 目っ！
Boo! Boo! Boo! Eyes on me!
めろめろ めろめろ ハート
Infatuated, infatuated heart,
膨らむ 膨らむ
Swelling up, swelling up!
見つめ直しましょう
Take another look at me!
あっぷっぷ！
Appuppu!
浮気？ 浮気？ うそー！
Cheating? Cheating? No way!
逃さないでしょ！
You won't let me escape, right?
目移りダメ！ ほんと イヤ、イヤ！
Looking away is a no-no! I really hate it, hate it!
いつも見て 見て 私も見てる！
Look at me, look at me always, I'm watching you too!
あなたが推してくれた 愛情の全開！
Full force of love that you gave by supporting me!
街は照らされる 太陽の差！
The town is illuminated, brighter than the sun!
LOVE LOVE LOVE 欲しく 四六時中
Wanting love, love, love 24/7!
とっても とっても とっても とっても 愛してほしい
I want you to love me so, so, so, so much!
ハッピー ハッピー ハッピー 最上級
Happy, happy, happy, top tier!
はっきり はっきり はっきり はっきり
Clearly, clearly, clearly, clearly!
心 ピコピコ 気持ちのバロメーター 超上がる！
Heart beeping, my feeling barometer soars!
推し変... 推し変...
Oshi-change... oshi-change...
もう ほんとに ほんとに ほんとに ほんとに わかってね！
Really, really, really, really understand, okay?!
おいみんな！ ここまでついてこれてる？
Hey everyone! Can you keep up so far?
この後も この調子で 行くよー！
Keep up this momentum for what's coming next!
ちょっと待って なんで他の子 褒めるの？
Wait a sec, why are you praising other girls?
よそ見禁止！ 怒っちゃうぞ！
No looking away! I'll get angry!
私以外の気になってるでしょ！
You're interested in someone other than me, aren't you?
ありえない！ ありえない！
No way! Impossible!
プンプン！ ほかの子に ちょ、ちょ、ちょ、ちょっとだけ
Pouting! Just a, a, a, a little bit to other girls,
よそ見したいよね？ うそ、マジ無理！
You wanna look away, right? No, seriously, I can't!
浮気お辞態じゃ！ 私を推すんじゃ！ 指切りしてよ 針千本！
Reject cheating! Support ME! Make a pinky promise, a thousand needles!
心変わりしたら 本当に すねる！ 怒る！ 泣いちゃうからね！
If you change your mind, I'll really pout! Get angry! Cry, okay?!
推し変は してないね？
You haven't changed your oshi, right?
私だけに 注目してね？
Pay attention only to me, okay?
だって ほら コメントが 愛に溢れている
Look, after all, the comments are overflowing with love!
瀕死のHP ミルミル回復！ 推し事レベルの パワーチャージ！
Dying HP rapidly recovering! Oshigoto-level power charge!
コメ！ コメ！ コメ！ 超コメ！ コメ！ コメ！ 超！
Comments! Comments! Comments! Super comments! Comments! Comments! Super!
LOVE LOVE LOVE 欲しく 四六時中
Wanting love, love, love 24/7!
いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい いっぱい 推してほしい！
I want you to support me so, so, so, so much!
推しの為 日々お仕事励んでくれて ありがとう！
Thank you for working hard every day for your favorite!
もっと推しを もっと愛しい
Love your favorite even more!
絶対！絶対！絶対！絶対！
Definitely! Definitely! Definitely! Definitely!
お願いね！
Please!
この！この！この！この！
This! This! This! This!
銀河の果てまで推してほしい！
Support us to the ends of the galaxy!
同じ未来を見ていたい
I want to look toward the same future,
あの夢手にしたい
I want to hold that dream in my hands.
それぞれ違ったココロで 走れ GO!
With our own unique hearts, run, go!
Shiny Smily Story
どこ見ても真っ暗な場所に芽生えてた
Sprouting in a place shrouded in darkness,
ほんの小さな希望に
a tiny ray of hope...
この瞳奪われた
captivated my eyes.
不安で揺れる心を上手くチューニングして
Tuning my heart whenever it wavers with anxiety,
ほんの小さな勇気を振り絞っていたよ
I summoned every bit of my tiny courage.
諦めの文字デリートして進む
I'll delete the word "give up" and keep moving forward.
苦しいときも もう私はひとりじゃないから
Even in painful times, I'm not alone anymore.
だからもっと夢追いかけたい
That's why I want to chase my dreams even more.
ワクワク止まらない
This excitement won't stop.
想像超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみたい
Want to access it?
後悔なんてさせない
I won't let you regret it.
それぞれ違ったココロで走れ GO!
With our own unique hearts, run, go!
仮想の空に輝く眩しい想いは
Dazzling feelings shining in the virtual sky
見たことのない光を現実にとどけるよ
will deliver a light never seen before into reality.
いつも聞こえるエールはここにキャプチャーして
Capturing the cheers I always hear right here,
また新しい光を探したくなるよ
it makes me want to search for new light again.
君の笑顔は保存して進む
Saving your smile as I press forward,
悲しいときに見返すよ力が湧くから
I look back on it when sad, because it gives me strength.
胸を張って夢追いかけたい
Holding my head high, I want to chase my dreams.
奇跡の物語一緒に作ろう 終わらない夢を
Let's create a miraculous story together, an endless dream.
誰一人欠かせない愛が舞ったこの世界
In this world where love dances, with no one left behind,
それぞれ違ったココロで彩れ
let's color it with our own unique hearts!
悲しいときも 寂しいときも
Even when sad, even when lonely,
信じ合えるものがある
there is something we can believe in together.
忘れずにこの鼓動鳴らし続けたい
Without forgetting, I want to keep this heartbeat pulsing.
終わらない世界に溢れ出すよ笑顔達
Smiles overflow in an endless world.
憧れの舞台立ちたい らしく輝きたい
I want to stand on the dream stage, shining as myself.
時に涙してまた笑い合いたい
Sometimes shedding tears, and smiling together again.
同じ未来を見たい あの夢手にしたい
I want to see the same future, to hold that dream.
踏み出そう奇跡の一歩を
Let's take that miraculous first step!
息切らして夢追いかけたい
Out of breath, I want to keep chasing my dream.
ワクワク止まらない
This excitement won't stop.
想像超えてく世界見せてあげる
I'll show you a world beyond imagination.
アクセスしてみない？
Won't you access it?
後悔なんてここにない
There are no regrets here.
それぞれ違ったココロで作る world
A world created with our own unique hearts!
みんなー！コーラは持ったかなー？
Everyone! Did you get your Coke?
持ってきたー！乾杯するー！
Got it! Let's toast!
こらこら、早いはラプラスちゃん！
Hey hey, too fast, La+-chan!
避けるな！当たるー！
Don't dodge! It's gonna hit!
年越しのタイミングで、みんなで乾杯ってするんだよ
At the turn of the year, everyone toasts and drinks together!
やだやだ！もう喉カラカラ！
No no! My throat is parched!
楽しみだね、ね？
Looking forward to it, right?
みこさん？みこさん？
Miko-san? Miko-san?
いやー、いいライブだったねー
Man, that was a great live show~
おつかれー イエーイ
Good work~ Yeah!
このあとどうするー？ご飯食べるー？
What should we do after this? Eat food?
いや、どこも混んでんじゃない？
Nah, isn't everywhere crowded?
確かにー。もう帰りますかねー
True. Guess we'll head home then.
あ、運転手さん！真っ直ぐで！
Ah, driver! Go straight!
お前達ー！何帰ってんだー！乾杯！乾杯！
You guys! Why are you heading home?! Cheers! Cheers!
フブちゃんたちが追っかけてきてるー
Fubu-chan and the others are chasing us!
あらあらフブちゃん、寂しくなっちゃったのかなー？
My my, Fubu-chan, did you get lonely?
なんか怒ってない？
Wait, aren't they angry?
えっ…あ！やばい！あのいたずらがバレたかなー？
Eh... Ah! Uh oh! Did they find out about that prank?
やりすぎだったっかー！ヤバいかもー！
Did we go too far?! This might be bad!
運転手さん、ごめん！
Driver, sorry!
みこのドラテクで逃げるぞー！
We're escaping with Miko's driving skills!
あ、来た！
Ah, they're here!
すごいすごいー！
Awesome, awesome!
フブちゃんごめんって！もう悪戯しないから！
Fubu-chan, we're sorry! We won't do pranks anymore!
ダメだよみこみこ！反省しなさい！
No way, Miko-miko! Reflect on what you did!
あんも共犯だろがー！
You're an accomplice too!
なんの話だよ！
What are you guys talking about?!
ふたりともこれ持ってー！
You two, hold this!
何するのー？
What are we doing?
もうすぐ新年だよ！
It's almost the New Year!
10, 9, 8, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3, 2, 1!
乾杯ー！
Cheers!
あけましておめでとうー！
Happy New Year!
今年もよろしくねー！
Looking forward to this year too!
今年もいっぱい遊ぼう！
Let's play a lot this year too!
言うよ！悪戯って何なの？
Say it! What was that prank?
あ、それね…
Ah, that...
フブちゃんのヘソ増やしたんだよ
We added more of Fubu-chan's belly buttons!
4つー？！
Four of them?!!
このあとはコカ・コーラと一緒にスペシャルライブステージ！
Next up, a Special Live Stage with Coca-Cola!
SPECIAL STAGE
そうさずっと 僕らの奇跡が
That's right, forever! May our miracle
途切れないように歌うんだ
never fade as we sing out.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Higher, with a bigger voice!
聞こえてた 何かが始まるサイン
Did you hear it? The sign that something is starting.
集まって 気づけば和音を奏でた
Gathering together, before we knew it, we played a chord.
夢に見るだけじゃ もう足りないでしょ？
Just dreaming about it isn't enough anymore, right?
キミを待ってる世界があるよ
There's a world waiting for you.
楽しい予感に ほら 飛び乗っちゃえばいい
Look, just jump onto this fun feeling!
トキメキは止められないから
Because the excitement can't be stopped,
走ろう！
let's run!
連れて行くよ！ 光の真ん中 夢の先へ
I'll take you there! Into the middle of the light, beyond the dream.
羽ばたける勇気は キミの願い
The courage to spread your wings is your wish.
皆で繋いだ この奇跡が
Connected by everyone, may this miracle
途切れないように歌うんだ
never fade as we sing out.
もっと高く 大きな声で
Higher, with a bigger voice!
答えとか 理屈に惑わされて
Flustered by answers and logic,
さまよっても 戻ってこれる場所があったんだ
even if we wander, there was a place we could return to.
地図にない道ゆく 僕らの旅
Traveling down uncharted roads on our journey,
願いだけが道標だよ
our wishes alone are our guiding sign.
夢の色が変わっても 変わらないメロディー
Even if the color of the dream changes, the melody remains unchanged.
キミのために 僕らのために 歌おう！
For you, for us, let's sing!
そうさきっと！ 僕らの奇跡は終わらないよ
That's right, surely! Our miracle will never end.
涙さえきっかけに変えていこう
Let's turn even tears into a new start.
信じてくれる仲間と一緒に
Together with friends who believe in us,
どこへだって飛び出していこう
let's leap out anywhere!
もっと遠く 空を越えて
Farther away, across the sky!
越えて...
Beyond...
いくよー！
Here we go!
未来の僕らに まだ見ぬキミに
To us in the future, to you whom we haven't met yet,
伝えたいこと たくさんあるんだ
there are so many things I want to tell you.
迎えたイマは 当たり前なんかじゃない
This present we've reached is not something taken for granted.
翼を広げ さあ今 飛ぼう！
Spread your wings, now let's fly!
Take my hand!
連れて行くよ！ 光の真ん中 夢の先へ
I'll take you there! To the center of light, beyond our dreams.
羽ばたける勇気は キミの願い
The courage to spread our wings comes from your wish.
皆で繋いだ この奇跡が
So that this miracle we all connected together
途切れないように 歌うんだ
will never break, we sing.
もっと高く！
Even higher!
大きな声で
With loud voices!
もっと高く！
Even higher!
大きな声で
With loud voices!
僕らの未来 彩って
Color our future,
どこまでも 響け Prism Melody
echo everywhere, Prism Melody!
Show Them (Who You Are)
Won't you just forget about the past?
'Cause in time it will never matter
But the love we had
I'm hoping it will last
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through it all
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan artinya 'kan cerahkanmu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten your future
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Hold tight to what you seek
Teriakan
Shout it out
La la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Bersama kita t'lah lewati
Together we have passed through it all
Tawa dan canda jadi memori
Laughter and jokes become memories
Pastikan artinya cerahkanmu nanti
Make sure its meaning will brighten your future
Cerahkanmu nanti
Will brighten your future
To do what you were meant to do
For it's time to make it true
Together we can always stand
Your hand in my hand
Forever hand in hand
Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming
Genggamlah yang kau cari
Hold tight to what you seek
Teriakan
Shout it out
La la la la la, la la la la la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
So go and travel far, run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La la la la la, la la la la la
Be who you meant to be
Gambar yo!
Jangan kau takut
Don't be afraid,
karena pada akhirnya
because in the end,
semua 'kan baik saja
everything will be okay.
Arahkan pandanganmu
Direct your gaze,
tajam lurus ke depan
straight ahead.
'Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
genggamlah yang kau cari
grasp what you're searching for,
teriakkan!
shout it out!
'Tuk mulai bermimpi
To start dreaming,
genggamlah yang kau cari
grasp what you're searching for,
teriakkan
shout it out
La-la-la-la-la
Kau takkan sendiri
You won't be alone
So go and travel far
Run and show them who you are
I'll be singing
La-la-la-la-la
Kau takkan pernah sendiri
You will never be alone
It's time to show them who you are
Just shout it from the mountain high
To the sky we go, we go
Just look around and see—it's so incredible!
So many smiles in a sea of light
Take one step with me and you'll be dazzled
There's magic in the air tonight
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
The world is brighter because you believe in me
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud
Our time is right now
We're on the edge of destiny
For a moment, I can dream with you
Every miracle we hoped for might come true
We come together, reaching out from far and wide,
and suddenly, you're here by my side!
When our voices and hearts unite,
we're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one!
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for,
the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing, all for one!
All for one!
Everything's in motion,
get up and start the celebration,
come see the wonders here beyond imagination
We're joining hands for the world to see,
feel the love and the energy!
The hours zoom, zoom, zoom
My heart goes boom, boom, boom
A dizzy whirlwind of dreams and reality
Let's shout it loud, loud, loud
Our time is right now
We're here together, finally!
Every moment takes my breath away;
there's a feeling here that words cannot convey,
we hear the rhythm and we rise to meet the song,
and suddenly, our hearts beat as one!
Every voice ringing loud and clear, so glad to be here
together, we're all for one.
Let's sing! All for one!
We'll sing in harmony and we'll be happy
jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!
Keep up the hype, it's good times, good vibes
Remember this night the rest of our lives
Hey!
Raise up your hands and sway, your light will lead our way,
we're shining, all for one!
All for one!
So bring your memories, your joy and your hope,
we'll gather and we'll sing upon this endless road, oh, oh
Feel the music in your passionate soul,
we're here right now, so let the good times roll, oh, oh
Every time that I'm with you,
I could swear it's like a wish is coming true
So I'll believe in you if you believe in me,
together we can chase all our dreams!
1, 2, 3, 4, 5!
When our voices and hearts unite, we're gonna shine bright together, we're all for one!
Let's sing! All for one!
The thrill of happiness is all around us!
Jump in, 'cause it's all for one
Let's sing! All for one!!
We're on our way to good times, good vibes
We'll treasure this day the rest of our lives
Hey!
All that we waited for, the dream we're striving toward,
we're singing, all for one! All for one!
皆さんあけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year, everyone!
Reach to the top, We are ReGLOSS!
ここからはホロライブDEV_ISコラボステージです！聴いてください、FG ROADSTER
From here on, it's the Hololive DEV_IS collab stage! Please listen to FG ROADSTER!
Let's go!
搭載 V8 エンジン
Equipped with a V8 engine
第7感持ってる原人
Primitive with a 7th sense
ロックするこの世界と全人類
Locking onto this world and all humanity
この5人でゲームをチェンジ
Changing the game with these 5
うなる4輪 発進準備
Roaring 4 wheels, preparing to launch
皆さんサンキュー サランヘヨ
Thank you everyone, saranghae
悦に浸ったのちては 取る一番ここから
After indulging in delight, taking number one from here
エゴ超えて挑戦
Challenging beyond ego
チャンスを載せた打線
Batting lineup loaded with opportunities
登りあげる頂点
Climbing to the top
座布団積んでく昇天
Stacking cushions to ascension
乗り込め FG ROADSTER
Hop on the FG ROADSTER
猛者達集合 能力差
Gathering of the fiercest, difference in skill
さあこの歴史名誉を頂戴
Now, give us this history and honor
ぶっちぎりの置き去り 恐怖心
Leaving terror far behind
超高速でぶち抜いていく体験
An experience of blasting through at super high speed
エンジンかジェットの炎
Engine or jet flame
揺れている階級へ
Toward the shaking hierarchy
広がる大地を越えていく海域線
Crossing the ocean boundary line over expanding land
バックミラーにビッグブルーが映ってる IVYW
Big Blue is reflected in the rearview mirror, IVYW
打ち上げたいから飛んでく宇宙船
A spacecraft flying off wanting to launch
この年月 果てしないです
These months and years are endless
銀河です 知識食べたい
It's a galaxy, I want to devour knowledge
燃えてるでかいビジョン 燃えてるメンバー一揆
Burning big vision, burning member uprising
ただいま現在 進行形 超えてく世界 規模
Right now in present progressive, crossing over on a world scale
体はモンスター 心がもう
My body is a monster, my heart is already...
Pariha
FG Pariha
光るデスモンスター
Glowing death monster
ヘビーブースター
Heavy booster
目覚めていく本能
Awakening instinct
青い炎
Blue flame
B.F.F. Let's go out
そう風になれ 0から
So become the wind, from zero
空まで とらわれ
Bound all the way to the sky
走る FG ROADSTER
Running FG ROADSTER
うなるブースター
Roaring booster
Long note Say with me
Imagination
あけましておめでとうございます！
Happy New Year!
ここからは私達FLOW GLOWがReGLOSS先輩の「フィーリンググラデーション」をカバーさせていただきます！
From here on, we FLOW GLOW will cover ReGLOSS seniors' "Feeling Gradation"!
ニコたんが来たー！
Niko-tan is here!
セクシーにいくぞ！しょぴしょぴまーん！
Let's go sexy! Shopi-shopi-maan!
愛でかい！Let's go! 我慢さーん！
Big love! Let's go! Gaman-san!
ちゃんまー！きらきらなー！うーん、ビビ！
Chan-ma! Sparkling! Mm, Vivi!
私のもとにおいで！
Come to me!
バイバイ 昨日の憂鬱なBeat
Bye-bye to yesterday's gloomy beat
紐解く Tissue
Untying tissue
さあ 様変わりして Show Time
Now, changing things up for Showtime
全然悪くない Imagination
Not bad at all, imagination
視界の霧は晴れ渡って
The fog in sight clears completely
悲しみには別れを告げ
Saying goodbye to sadness
酸いも甘いも宙に放り出して
Throwing both bitter and sweet into the air
滲む空 描くは薔薇色を
The blurring sky paints a rose color
どれだけ上手く見せようとしても
No matter how well I try to put on a front
君がいなければ 何の意味もない
If you're not here, it means nothing at all
かすり傷すらつかない嘘
A lie that doesn't even leave a scratch
針の生えないレコードさ
It's a record with no needle
鮮やかなグラデーション 風にして
Turn vibrant gradation into the wind
Come on, let's roll!
どこか吹き荒れる追い風にも心
Even in the tailwind blowing somewhere
なびかせて
letting my heart sway
飛び出せ To the future
Leap out to the future
Restart the light, hey!
透明系 Shimmer
Transparent shimmer
瞬く間に広がる解放感
A sense of release spreading in an instant
1つ1つ全てが Drama
Every single thing is drama
街は見慣れたベネチアンライト Hey!
The town is familiar Venetian light, hey!
変わり変わる色 パノラマ
Ever-changing color panorama
満ちあふれる Feeling gradation
Overflowing feeling gradation
飛び出せ Your image
Leap out, your image
恐れるものはない
There is nothing to fear
Restart the light, hey!
綺麗な朝焼けが
The beautiful morning glow
透明な明日を照らすよ
illuminates a clear tomorrow
Restart the light, hey!
せーの、ありがとうございました！
One, two, thank you so much!
最後の曲は！
The final song is...
Our Bright Parade!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
輝くんだよ
Shine bright
呼び合う声を
with calling voices
合図に
as the signal!
Parade, Parade, Parade!
探しにゆく
Going out to search
スタートは何度だって
No matter how many times we start anew
ただ 独り言を綴った
I simply jotted down my inner thoughts
ただ 始まりたくて走った
I ran just wanting something to begin
遠く 暗がりに灯った
Lit up in the distant darkness,
それは 眩しすぎた名前
it was a name far too dazzling
それは 優しすぎる思い出 もっと
Those memories were far too gentle—
近づけと手を伸ばした
I reached out my hand to get closer
思いがけず結び合った
Unexpectedly, our bonds connected
ほら 今
Look, right now
迷子は“僕等”になった
lost children became "us"
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along the regrets and the love as well
風、夢、羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes the light
終わりなき兆し
A never-ending sign
君を見つけたこと 胸を張れるよ
Finding you is something I can be proud of
ここから
From here on
これから
From now on
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
まだ 頼りない予感を
A still uncertain premonition—
歌おう 恥ずかしくなんてないよ
let's sing it, there's nothing to be ashamed of
誰も解けない イマジナリー
An imaginary world no one can unravel
いつか また逢えるおまじない
A spell that ensures we'll meet again someday
あの日 ゼロに始まった ストーリー
The story that started from zero that day
数え切れない 言の葉
Countless words
数えるような 想いじゃないさ
Feelings aren't something you can just count
ほら 今
Look, right now
“僕等”を一つと呼ぼう
let's call "us" one and the same
Parade, Parade, Parade! 美しいんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! It's so beautiful!
許し合える刹那 夜はきらめく
Moments of mutual understanding make the night sparkle
雨、晴れ、カレイド またとない空
Rain, sunshine, kaleidoscope—a one-of-a-kind sky
ふさわしい旅路とは
What makes a worthy journey
君と在ることさ
is simply being with you
君と在ることなんだ
It's all about being with you
“ただいま”を聞けば
Whenever I hear "I'm back,"
“おかえり”って叫ぶよ
I'll shout "Welcome home!"
当たり前じゃないか
Isn't that natural?
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We're gonna shine!
暗がりを満たすのは
What fills up the darkness
君だ 僕だ!
is you, and me!
Parade, Parade, Parade! 輝くんだよ
Parade, Parade, Parade! We're gonna shine!
悔しさも愛しさも連れておいで
Bring along the regrets and the love as well
風、夢、羽根 飛び立てるさ
Wind, dreams, wings—we can take flight!
ささやかな祈りは光
A modest prayer becomes the light
終わりなき兆し
A never-ending sign
君と飛び込んでゆく 素敵なスタートさ
Diving in together with you—what a wonderful start!
ここから
From here on
これから
From now on
Our Bright Parade, Parade!
キャスト
[Cast]
セットリスト
[Setlist]
この後は もう1本グランプリ！ 2026年もホロライブプロダクションをよろしくお願い致します！
Up next: Mou Ippon Grand Prix! We look forward to your continued support of Hololive Production in 2026!